https://www.studsandspikes.com/privacy/

Privacy Notice
| StudsandSpikes.com
Contact
Login
Cart (no items)
Privacy Notice
We know you care how information about you is used and shared, and we appreciate your trust. This notice describes our privacy policy. By visiting this site, you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy Notice.
The information we learn from customers helps us personalize and continually improve your shopping experience. We use the information that you provide for such purposes as responding to your requests, customizing future shopping for you, improving our stores, and communicating with you.
If you do not want to receive e-mail or other mail from us, please adjust your Customer Communication Preferences.
Do We Share Information We Receive?  Information about our customers is an important part of our business, and we are not in the business of selling or renting it to "others".
Who qualifies as "others":  Well.... if it`s not you or us then it`s them. They`re the others.
Agents:  We may on occasion employ others to perform functions on our behalf. Examples include fulfilling orders, delivering packages, sending postal mail and e-mail, removing repetitive information from customer lists, analyzing data, providing marketing assistance, processing credit card payments, and providing customer service. They have access to information needed to perform their functions, but may not use it for other purposes.
Business Transfers:  As we continue to develop our business, we might sell or buy stores or assets. In such transactions, customer information generally is one of the transferred business assets. Also, in the unlikely event that our assets are acquired, customer information will of course be one of the transferred assets.
Protection of We and Others:  We release account and other personal information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with law; enforce or apply our Conditions of Use and other agreements; or protect the rights, property, or safety of this site, our users, or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organizations for fraud protection and credit risk reduction.
Children and Youth  This site does not sell products for purchase by children. We can sell children's products for purchase by adults. If you are under 18, you may use this site only with involvement of a parent or guardian.
SHOP BY CATEGORY:
STUDS
PyramidConical ConeEnglish Punk 77DomeJewel SetSpecialty ShapeGarment MP StudsJacket Collection
SPIKES
Tree SpikesGiant Tree SpikesHex SpikesCone SpikesClaw Spikes24kt Gold SpikesSpecial Spikes
BELTS
Studded BeltsM60 Bullet Belts .308M16 Bullet Belts .223M77 Punk Bullet Belt
